ACTWU's Research Department Records 5619/016
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Statements - Perkel, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Statements - Potofsky, Jacob S., 1921-1949 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Statements - Potofsky, Jacob S., 1950-1954 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Statements - Potofsky, Jacob S., 1955-1964 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Statements - Potofsky, Jacob S., 1965-1971 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Statements -Rosenblum, Frank, 1930-1971 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Statements -Sheinkman, Jacob, 1961-1983 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Statements - Peterson, Esther, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Statements - Samuel, Howard, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Statements - General Executive Board, 1977-1982 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Statements - Simon, Louis, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Foreign Trade Statements on Foreign Trade, 1959-1972 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Dow Chemical Co. - IUD Study, 1976-1989 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Dresser Industries, Inc. (IUD Study), 1966 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Drug and Cosmetic Conference (IUD Study - Parts I & II), 1966-1971 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Dominion Bridge Co. (IUD Study), 1981 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Office of the Special Representative for Trade Negotiations, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- AFL-CIO Wage & Price Stability, Council On, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Foreign Trade - Gloves, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Foreign Trade Multilateral Agreements, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- CPI Testimony (Methodology), 1981 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Trade Adjustment Assistance, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- AFL-CIO Positions - Blackwell, Ron, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- AFL-CIO Resolutions & Statements, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America - Technologies, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Work and Technology Institute, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Technology and Work Organization, 1993-1996 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- AMCA - Koehring (IUD Study), 1983-1986 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- AMF Incorporated (IUD Study), 1980-1983 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Akzona, Inc. (IUD Study), 1976 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Allegheny International (IUD Study), 1985 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Allied Signal Corporation (IUD Study), 1983-1991 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- American Brake Shoe Company (IUD Study), 1965 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- American Cyanamid Co. (IUD Study), 1981 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- American Hardware Construction (IUD Study), 1965 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- American Home Products Corporation (IUD Study), 1977 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- American Radiator & Standard Sanitary Corporation (IUD Study), 1966 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Anaconda American Brass Company (IUD Study), 1966 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Appliance Industry (IUD Study), 1988 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Armstrong Cork Co. - II (IUD Study), 1984-1994 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- BASF Corp. (IUD Study), 1986-1989 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- BTR, Inc. (IUD Study), 1991-1993 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Battery Industry (IUD File), 1994 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- ACTWU + EPI (Economic Policy Institute), 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- EPI (Economic Policy Institute): A Conference on Trade, Competitiveness and American Living Standards, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- EPI (Economic Policy Institute): Seminar on Macroeconomic Policy, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- EPI (Economic Policy Institute): Untying the Economic Knot, Faux, Jeff, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- EPI (Economic Policy Institute): Sheinkman, Jack, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- EPI (Economic Policy Institute): Teamwork Economics, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- EPI (Economic Policy Institute): Rothstein Report, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- NAFTA Bibliographies, 1993-1995 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- NAFTA Magazine Articles, 1990-1993 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- NAFTA Journal Articles, 1990-1994 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- NAFTA Newspaper Articles/Press Releases, 1993-1995 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- NAFTA Memo/Announcements, 1991-1995 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Cannon Mills: Cannonball Express, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Cannon Mills: Attitude Surveys, 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Cannon Mills: News Clippings, 1985-1991 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Cannon Mills: Labor, 1982-1986 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Cannon Mills: ACTWU Labor, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Clifton Yarns Mills, 1972-1978 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Clothes Connection, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Coca-Cola Drivers, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Colecraft Manufacturing Co. Lancaster, NY, 1971-1975 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Colgate Plastics Co., 1973-1975 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Concord Fabrics, 1970-1987 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Cone Mills Corp.-- Revolution Organizing Committee (ROC), 1978-1985 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Cone Mills Corp. (Parras Industries - Mexico), 1992-1994 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Cone Mills Corp. (Research Project), 1980 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Cone Workers' Union Voice, 1980-1982 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Courtaulds Fibers, Inc., 1973-1993 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Courtaulds Fibers, Inc. (Labor) (Courtaulds, Ala.) - Mobile & Le Moyne, Alabama., 1972-1987 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Craftex Mill, Inc. of PA, 1974-1998 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Cranston Print Works Co., 1979-1996 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Cranston Print Works Co. (Fletcher, NC), 1957-1985 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Dan River Inc. Plant, Clifton S.C, 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Damas Atlantic Ltd. - NLRB, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Damon, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  English, Spanish
- Decorative Surfaces International, 1973-1989 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Delta Woodside Industries, Inc. (Stanwood Corp.,), 1958-1988 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Devro Co. Somerville, N.J., 1961-1991 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- DG Trim Products, 1992-1993 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Dial Corporation, 1991-1994 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Dominion Textile Inc. (Financial & General), 1975-1995 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Down Carpet Co., 1971-1991 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Dowty Group. Dowty (USA) Holdings, Inc., 1990-1991 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Duro Industries, Inc., 1977-1989 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Dyers-Metro Area (Wage Survey), 1980 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Dyers - Metropolitan Area, 1980-1994 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- E-B Industries, Inc., 1979-1993 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Eagle Knitting Mills Milwaukee, Wisc., 1965-1978 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Elder Manufacturing Co., 1992 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Emerson Electric Co., 1964-2002 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Exxon Chemical Co. (USA) (Subs. of Exxon Corp.), 1973-1987 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Farah, 1974-1998 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Farris Fashions, Inc., 1991-1994 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. (News clipping), 1976-1997 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Fieldcrest Cannon, Inc. (Financial & General), 1986-1997 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Freudenberg Nonwovens Limited Partnership (formerly: Pellon Corp.), 1973-1991 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Hanes Corp. (Organizing Campaign), 1981-1983 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Hawes Corp., 1981-1983 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Harriet Cotton Mills, 1956-1982 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Jantzen, Inc. (News clippings), 1963-1979 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Jason, Inc., 1971-1993 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Jay Garment Co., 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Jefferson Mills, Inc. (Pulaski, VA), 1972-1983 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- J H Collectibles Inc., 1990-1994 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- J.H. Rutter-Rex Mfg. Co., Inc., 1958-1992 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Jockey International, Inc. (Cooper's, Inc.) Cedartown, Georgia, 1960-1993 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Jockey International, Inc. Millen, GA, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Jockey International, Inc. (Blue Grass Knitting, Inc.) Carlisle, KY, 1970-1986 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Jomac, Inc., 1963-1981 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Jones. Fred Mfg. Co., 1993 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Jonbil, Inc., 1967-1987 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- JPS Textile Group, Inc. 1988-1996 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Johnson & Johnson (Financial & General), 1990-1996 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Johnson & Johnson (Financial & General), 1989 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Johnson & Johnson (Financial & General), 1983-1988 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Johnson & Johnson (Financial & General), 1968-1982 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Johnson & Johnson (General Labor), 1972-1995 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Johnson & Johnson (Foreign Unions), 1987 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Johnson & Johnson Cornelia, GA, 1980-1982 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Johnson & Johnson (Chicopee Mills) Gainesville, GA., 1978-1984 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Johnson & Johnson (Benson, N.C.), 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Johnson & Johnson (Arbrook, Inc.) Arlington, Texas, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Johnson & Johnson Albuquerque, N.M., 1982-1988 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Johnson & Johnson (Puerto Rico Operations), 1980-1991 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Johnson & Johnson (Organizing Probe Reports), 1980-1982 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Johnson & Johnson (Chicago, Ill.) (Local 1437), 1972-1982 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Johnson & Johnson (New Brunswick, N.J.), 1959-1988 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Johnson & Johnson (New Brunswick, N.J.) (1959 Arbitration) (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Johnson & Johnson (Ortho Division), 1977-1982 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Johnson & Johnson (ACTWU J&J Advisory Council), 1981-1987 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- J.P. Stevens & Co., Inc. (News clipping), 1982-1999 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- J.P. Stevens & Co., Inc.(General Labor), 1974-1995 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- J.P. Stevens & Co., Inc. (Financial & General), 1974-1995 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Kalkstein Silk Mills, Inc., 1989-1992 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Kenfall International, Inc., 1964-1993 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Kendall Co. Newberry, SC, 1972-1982 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Kendall Co. Walpole, Mass., 1970-1984 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Kimberly-Clark Corp. (Berkeley Mills), 1971-1975 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Kitaura Spinning Co., 1989-1991 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Kleen Brite Laboratories, Inc., 1973-1999 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Cone Mills Corp, 1984-1992 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Klote International Corp., 1980-1997 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Kosins Clothes, Inc., 1991 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Kraft Hat Mfg. Inc., 1978-1991 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Knoxville Glove Co., 1966-1967 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Koracorp Industries, Inc. (Financial & General), 1978-1991 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Lake Butler Apparel Co., 1960-1966 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Levi Strauss & Co. (News clippings), 1990-1998 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Levi Strauss & Co. (News clippings), 1984-1989 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Levi Strauss & Co. (News clippings), 1971-1983 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Levi Strauss & Co. (Financial & General), 1988-1991 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Levi Strauss & Co. (Subs. of Santone Industries), 1980-1992 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Levi Strauss & Co., 1992-1994 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Levi Strauss & Co. (Financial & General), 1969-1987 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Lewistown "Specialty" Yarns, Inc., 1990-1994 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- W.S. Libbey Co., 1972-1991 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Lichtenberg, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Lichtenberg, 1986-1999 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- S. Lichtenberg & Co. (Financial & General), 1987-1994 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- S. Lichtenberg & Co. (Title VII Research), 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- S. Lichtenberg & Co.(News clippings), 1989-1997 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- S. Lichtenberg & Co. (Samsons Mfg. Co., Subs.) Affirmative Action Plan, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- S. Lichtenberg & Co. (Delila Manufacturing Co., Subs.) Affirmative Action Plan, 1989-1991 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Londontown Corp. (Financial & General), 1975-1995 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- M. Lowenstein Corporation, Rock Hill Printing & Finishing Division, Rock Hill, S.C., 1975-1988 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- M M G Corp., 1986-1988 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- M. Fine & Sons, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- MacClenny Products, Inc., 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Macy's, R.H. & Co., 1989-1995 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Magee Industrial Enterprises, Inc. (Employee Involvement Program), 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Bruno Magli, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Magna International, Inc., 1990 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Maid Bess Corp., 1988-1993 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Malden Mills, Inc. Mountainside, N.J., 1973-1984 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Malden Mills, Inc., 1970-1996 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Malden Mills, Inc. (Barre Mills, Div.) Barre Vermont, 1970-1981 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Manetta Mills, Inc., 1980-1995 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Manchester Knitted Fashions, Inc., 1962-1991 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Manhattan Coat Corp., 1993 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Manhattan Industries, Inc. (News clipping), 1976-1993 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Manhattan Industries, Inc. (Berkeley Cravats, Subs.), 1971-1989 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Manhattan Industries, Inc. (Financial and General), 1977-1988 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Manhattan Industries, Inc. (Acquisitions & Closings), 1974-1982 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Manhattan Industries, Inc. (Licensees U.S. & Overseas), 1977-1985 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Marks & Spencer - (Brooks Bros.) (Pension Documents) [Folder 1 of 2], 1982-1988 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Marks & Spencer - (Brooks Bros.) (Pension Documents) [Folder 2 of 2], 1984-1988 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Marks & Spencer - (Brooks Bros.) (Financial and General), 1990-1996 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Marks & Spencer - (Brooks Bros.) (News clippings), 1958-1993 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Marks & Spencer - (Brooks Bros.) (Financial & General), 1956-1989 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Marks & Spencer - (Brooks Bros.) ACTWU Dispute, Paterson, NJ, 1978-1979 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Marks & Spencer - (Brooks Bros.) (Pension Analysis/Correspondence), 1989 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Marks & Spencer PLC (Annual Reports), 1990-1995 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Masland Corp., 1970-1995 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Master Wear Corp., 1963-1984 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- May Department Stores Co. (News clippings), 1961-198 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- May Department Stores Co. (Report), 1994-1997 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- McGinley Mills Inc, 1983-1989 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Melville Corp. (Financial & General), 1961-1992 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Milliken & Co.(Formerly: Deering Milliken) (Financial & General), 1980-1995 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Milliken & Co.(Formerly: Deering Milliken) (Darlington Mfg. Co.,), 1978-1988 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Milliken & Co.(Formerly: Deering Milliken) (Darlington Mfg. Co.,), 1968-1977 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Milliken & Co.(Formerly: Deering Milliken) (News clipping), 1974-1990 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Munsingwear, Inc. (News clippings), 1977-1991 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Munsingwear, Inc. Ashland, Wis., 1980 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Munsingwear, Inc. Fairmont, N.C., 1980 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Munsingwear, Inc. Winnfield, Louisiana, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Munsingwear, Inc. (Financial and General), 1977-1989 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Munsingwear, Inc. Minneapolis, Minn., 1976-1989 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Oneita Industries, Inc. (Annual Reports), 1991-1995 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Oneita Industries, Inc. (Strike & Boycott, 1973) (Box 18, Folder 17)
- PPG Industries, Inc. Pittsburgh, PA, 1972-1994 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Palm Beach Inc. (Calvin Clothing, Inc., Subs.), 1967-1990 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Palm Beach Inc. (Financial & General), 1971-1995 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Parker Hannifin Corp., 1972-1987 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Paxar Corp., 1975-1995 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Peerless Clothing Inc., 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Pendleton Woolen Mills, Inc. (Financial & General), 1958-1988 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Permacel, Inc., 1981-1998 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Phoenix Dye Works Inc., 1972-1992 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Phoenix Medical Technology, Inc., 1981-1994 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Phillips-Van Heusen Corp. (News clipping), 1980-1995 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Chesebrough-Ponds (Bass Shoe Co.,), 1979-1984 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Pike Mfg. Co. (See also: Garment Corp of America), 1968-1991 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Pillowtex Corp./Fieldcrest Cannon, inc. (Tobacco Suits), 1968-1999 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Rapid-American Corp. (McGregor-Doniger, Inc., Subs.), 1979-1981 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Rapid-American Corp. (Wonderknit, subs.), 1980-1990 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Rapid-American Corp. (Anvil Knitwear, subs.), 1956-1990 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Rapid-American Corp. (News clipping), 1970-1991 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Rapid-American Corp. (McGregor Corp., subs.) (Correspondence & News clipping), 1983-1994 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Rapid-American Corp. (BVD Co., Subs.), 1961-1968 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Rapid-American Corp. (McCrory, subs.) (News clipping), 1971-1990 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- St. Francis Rehabilitation Hospital & Nursing Home, 1968-1987 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- SCT Yarns, Inc. (News clippings), 1966-1993 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- SCT Yarns, Inc. (Correspondence), 1977-1987 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- SCT Yarns, Inc. (Washington, GA), 1980-1982 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- SCT Yarns, Inc. (Boaz Spinning Co.) Boaz, AL, 1977-1983 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- SCT Yarns, Inc. (Thatcher Plant Closing,1988) Chattanooga, TN (Box 20, Folder 6)
- SCT Yarns, Inc. (Guntersville,AL), 1982 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Salant Corp. (Obion-Denton, Subs.), 1967-1991 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Samsonite Corp., 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Samsung Group, 1989-1990 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Santee Print Works, Inc. Sumpter, S.C., 1979-1988 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Sara Lee Corp. (Courtaulds Textiles PLC) (Financial & General), 1976-1996 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Sara Lee Corp. (Subs., Champion Products) (1978 File), 1967-1978 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Sara Lee Corp. (Subs., Adams-Millis) (Financial & General), 1972-1989 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Sara Lee Corp. (Courtaulds Textiles PLC) (News clipping), 1967-1996 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Schlegel Corp. (Employee Involvement Program), 1989-1996 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Schlegel Corp. (Financial & General), 1972-1989 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Schott Brothers, Inc., 1979-1993 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Schlegel Corp. (Financial & General), 1980-1991 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Schoeller, Inc. Sumter, S.C., 1977-1988 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Schoeneman, J. Inc., 1989-1995 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- M. Lowenstein - Pacific-Columbia Mills (Columbia, SC), 1973-1982 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Sheldahl, Inc (Financial & General), 1987-1990 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Smurfit-Stone Container Corp. (Alton Box Board Co.), 1968-1982 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Solomon Co. Inc., 1957-1966 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Springs Industries, Inc. (Graber Co., Subs.), 1975-1982 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Spring Industries, Inc. (Plant Lists), 1989-1993 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Spray Cotton Mills, Inc. (Subs. of Spray Textured Yarns, Inc.), 1972-1982 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Smith, Caleb V. & Son, Inc., 1975-1987 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Swany U.S.A. Corp., 1986-1990 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Takata Corp. (Financial & General), 1989-1990 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Tappan Co. (J-Wood), 1980-1990 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Texfi Industries, Inc. (Financial & General), 1980-1993 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- TextileLeather Co., 1975-1995 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Texprint, Inc., 1980-1993 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Tri-Con Industries Ltd., 1994 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Tultex Corp. (Financial & General), 1977-2000 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Tultex Corp., 1990 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Tultex, 1989-1990 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Tultex Corp. (News clipping), 1971-1994 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- United Merchants & Manufacturers, Inc. (Arkwright Finishing) Fall River, Mass., 1978-1992 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- U.S. Industries, Inc. (W.D. Byron & Sons, Inc.) Williamsport, MD, 1977-1995 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Unitog Co. (Financial & General), 1965-1992 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Black Workers for Justice, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Glenoit Mills, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Globe Albany Corp., 1972-1977 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- W.R. Grace & Co., 1975-1984 (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Gold Mills, Inc., 1969-1988 (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Goldtex Corp., 1990 (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Good Quality Sewing, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 28)
- Goody's Family Clothing, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- Goodyear Tire and Rubber Company, 1972-1975 (Box 21, Folder 30)
- Goya, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 31)
- Greenfield Research, Inc. (GRI), 1991-1994 (Box 21, Folder 32)
- Riverside, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 33)
- Gitman Bros., 1991 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Gilmore Trading Company, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Genesco, Inc. (Greif Companies), 1944-1993 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Harvey Clothing Co., 1967 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Gerber-Bates Products, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- G.H.R. Industries - Marissa, 1994-1995 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Hanes Corp, 1979-1984 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Hammond Manufacturing, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- HaggarCorporation. (Apparel), 1954-1996 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Gurney MFG. Co., 1979 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Kayser-Roth, 1968-1984 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Guilford Industries (Interface Inc.), 1990 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Suzy Curtains, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Vittadini, Adrienne Inc., 1994 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- WWG Industries, Inc. (Trend Mills, Inc.), 1977-1996 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Warren Corp. (Italian Union - Correspondence), 1988-1991 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  English and Italian
- Warren Corp., 1984-1996 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Warren Featherbone Co., 1987-1994 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Wellman, Inc. (Financial & General), 1987-1995 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Wellman, Inc. (News clipping), 1978-1995 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Wellman, Inc. (Fiber Industries, Subs.), 1979-1989 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Wellman, Inc. (Job Evaluation System), 1985-1987 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Wellman, Inc.(Annual Reports), 1987-1995 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Wellman, Inc. (Safety and Health Issues), 1980-1984 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Wellman, Inc. (Financial & General), 1976-1986 (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Wells Lamont Corp. (Subs. of Marmon Group, Inc.), 1963-1994 (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Welsh Co., 1966-1995 (Box 22, Folder 27)
- Westbrook Spinning Co., 1991-1992 (Box 22, Folder 28)
- West Mill Clothes Inc., 1968-1995 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- Wayn-Tex, Inc., 1976-1992 (Box 22, Folder 30)
- Westpoint Stevens, Inc. (S.E.C. Reports), 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Westpoint Stevens, Inc. Drakes Branch, VA, 1948-1988 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Westpoint Stevens, Inc. Lindale, GA, 1978-1986 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Westpoint Stevens Corp. (Valley Fashions Corp.), 1993 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Westpoint Stevens, Inc. Biddeford, ME, 1974-1991 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Westpoint Stevens, Inc. (Annual Reports), 1995 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Westpoint Stevens, Inc. -Blackstone, 1993-2000 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Westpoint Stevens, Inc. (Financial & General), 1977-1995 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Westpoint Stevens, Inc. (News clipping), 1966-1995 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Whiting, E.B. & A.C. Co., Inc., 1971-1995 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Fred Wilkinson Associates, Inc. (Wilkinson Textiles), 1989-1991 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Wolverine World Wide, Inc., 1979-1994 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Work Wear Corp., Inc. (News clipping), 1973-1991 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Work Wear Corp., Inc. (Financial & General), 1968-1985 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Yale Co-operative Corp., 1989-1997 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- YKK (U.S.A.), Inc., 1973-1989 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Yocom Knitting Co., 1983-1991 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- YSLA Designs, 1969-1992 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Work Wear Corp., Inc., 1977-1992 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- YSK Corp., 1994 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Yorke Shirt Co., 1989-1992 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Zeta Consumer Products Corp. (Financial & General), 1992-1997 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Zwicker Knitting Mills, 1959-1992 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- LDR - D.2.c - A-1 Shirt Laundry Piece Rates, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- LDR - D.2.c - ACE Shirt Laundry Piece Rates, 1950-1952 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- LDR - F Active Shirt Laundry Piece Rates, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- LDR - D.2.c - Active Shirt Piece Rates, 1945-1946 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- LDR - D.2.c - Advance Piece Rates, 1945-1946 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- LDR - D.2.c - Alabama Piece Rates, 1951 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- LDR - D.2.c - Allma Shirt Piece Rates, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- LDR - D.2.c - Andber Piece Rates, 1947 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- LDR - D.2.c - Art Shirt Piece Rates, 1945-1946 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- LDR - F - Art Shirt Laundry Piece Rates, 1948-1955 (Box 24, Folder 10)